windsurfercrs.com 2010-04-13

# Privacy policy. Stated. | whiteboardLabs

Your privacy is important to us. We want you to know that when you use our web site, your personally identifiable information will be respected and protected. The following are guidelines for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to the WhiteboardLabs.com site.

When you subscribe or make a request online, we collect specific information to potentially include your name, address, email address, and telephone numbers. This information is used by our team to communicate with you in regards to requested information.

**Emails**  
We use email addresses to deliver information relevant to our clients and friends, such as articles, newsletters, surveys, and notification services. As with information collected in conjunction with registration on WhiteboardLabs.com, email addresses will not be shared with third parties.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small information text files that are stored on your computer hard drive by your web browser. Cookies help establish a user session and allow our server to correctly provide site users with the appropriate information, advertisements and services. We also use cookies to ensure you obtain the information you request and to authenticate your authority to access the sitou can configure your browser to not accept cookies if you choose.

**Other Uses**  
We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law, court order, or as requested by a governmental or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable.

**Opting-Out**  
As a member of WhiteboardLabs.com, you will occasionally receive emails with articles and other noteworthy news items. We hope you will find these updates interesting and informative. Of course, if you would rather not receive this information, all email sent to you will contain a message on how to opt-out of communications in the future.

**Consent**  
By using this web site, you agree to the collection and use, consistent with applicable laws, of information available on or through this site (including your personally identifying information). Should a change to our privacy policy occur, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the nature of the information we collect, how we use it, and the circumstances under which we disclose it. Unless otherwise required or permitted by applicable law, we do not intend to use your personally identifiable information collected through this site in ways not described here without first providing you the opportunity to opt-out of that use.

**Other Sites**  
This privacy policy covers only the WhiteboardLabs.com website, and does not cover any other site, including those linked from this site. We have no control over other sites' privacy policies or use of any personal information you or others may share with them. Please do not assume that our Privacy Policy covers those other sites.
